Your grandmother made my graduation dress.
No wonder it looked horrible
in the photos.
-And did you have a boyfriend then?
-Yes.
Was he handsome?
I haven't seen any pictures.
Luckily. there were no cell phones
or social media back in the day.
And yes. he was handsome.
but never as handsome as your dad.
Nobody is more handsome than my dad.
Nobody.
Mom. can I ask you
for a special graduation gift?
After my party. I want to go
to an after-party with my friends.
Victoria is coming!
There are tables and chairs outside.
We hired several waiters.
There's a stage
for you to sing with your dad.
So why don't you invite everyone
and have the after-party here?
There are no parents at the after-party.
I promise I won't drink.
even if they try to force me.
Let's ask your dad.
In the name of our president.
I approve of this.
-Your dad will drive you and pick you up.
-Of course.
But first. miss.
let's do a mic check.
-Yes.
-Okay?
Whose eyes are those?
Dad. I'm almost 18.
Yours.
My makeup.
I love you.
We're so proud of you. sweetheart.
And that's why we have a surprise for you.
it's your graduation gift.
and there's a whole committee
waiting for you. so let's go.
Okay. I'm coming. Just give me a second.
-Yes. Let's go.
-Don't take too long.
-She's coming!
-Did she dress up?
Enough.
Ready?
What could this be?
Nana.
-No way!
-Yeah!
-No! Is it what I'm thinking?
-Yes!
Bravo!
You're going to let me drive it?
I'm a bit strict for your own good.
That's why I took you to get your license.
Congratulations again. Do you like it?
Sweetheart. you deserve everything.
You earned it.
You've been working so hard
since your illness started.
You're the coolest of the three of us.
You're going to ruin your makeup
if you cry. you know?
Come on. let's hug.
Sotomayor hug!
Congratulations!
Look who's here.
Victoria!
Check out my graduation gift!
-Yolanda. how are you?
-Fine. and you?
-Hi. Maria.
-Hi.
-Nice to see you. Yolanda.
-Emilio.
-Thanks for having us.
-It's our pleasure. Thanks for coming.
Your mom's letting you go
to the after-party?
Yes!
After-party? Victoria hasn't asked us
for permission to go to any after-party.
Did she tell you anything?
Juana told me
that a lot of cute boys are coming.
No way!
Ever since she turned 18.
she thinks she's her own boss.
Yeah. you have no idea
what you're in for when Julieta turns 18.
-Let's not even talk about it. Come in.
-We're not there yet.
I'm losing my virginity tonight!
Oh. yeah!
Grandpa. you scared me.
-Congratulations!
-Grandpa!
Love you. honey!
There you go!
Somewhere in a large country
Ricardo and Julieta are one and the same.
People forgot to build
And Maca just won't quit.
She's danced with all the guests.
A place where the sun won't burn you
My grandkids and my son
are professional artists.
…don't have to die
Julieta!
What happened?
Julieta. sweetheart!
No. There's no time for an ambulance.
Let's go.
Excuse me!
There's no time for an ambulance.
Let's go.
-Please. pick her up.
-Okay.
-Careful.
-Excuse me.
Careful.
Careful. Please. be careful.
Let's go.
MY DAUGHTER'S FATHER
CREATED BY ROBERTO STOPELLO
CENTRAL STANDARD TIME
I'LL TEXT YOU AS SOON
AS WE KNOW SOMETHING. LOVE YOU.
Maca.
How is she?
-What's with the face?
-You had blood drawn?
Yes. She had a severe crisis.
but she's responding to treatment now.
How serious is it?
The moment we were dreading is here.
Julieta urgently needs a transplant…
-But--
-But what?
Your kidney is a match for hers. right?
Julieta's blood protein levels
are significantly abnormal.
That's why I ordered a special test.
And we found a genetic disorder.
What does this have to do
with Julieta's transplant?
It's called Alport syndrome.
It's asymptomatic in most women.
and since they both have it.
the transplant wouldn't work.
Is it hereditary?
Yes. Your mom probably inherited it
from her parents or grandparents.
and Julieta from Maca or her grandparents.
It could also come from my family. right?
It's impossible to know
without a DNA test.
Well. test me to see if I'm a match.
if I have the syndrome. DNA. everything.
-I'm doing it too.
-Me too.
Thank you. Thank you.
The embarrassment of the year.
I hope no one posts it on Instagram.
I want to go home.
I want to drive my new car.
Of course. sweetheart.
Your kidneys are acting up.
You're sugarcoating bad news. right?
Am I going to die?
-No.
-Of course not. sweetheart.
You just need some backup.
A kidney transplant. as soon as possible.
So. are you going to have
just one kidney now?
I'd give you both if I could.
But we discovered something.
Mom can't donate it anymore. but your
brothers and I are going to get tested.
Everything will be fine. sweetheart. Okay?
Stop arguing with your mom. Julieta.
Can't you see she's always scolding me?
My dear! It's so good to see you back!
I'll take this.
Thank you.
From now on.
you can't miss a single dialysis.
-No excuses.
-Stop it.
-You're not a nephrologist.
-Hey. Julieta!
This is serious.
We have to be stricter
with what we eat in this house. please.
Stricter?
I always cook according to her diet--
Hey!
You've been secretly eating junk food.
haven't you? Did you drink at the party?
Could you two calm down. please? Maca!
How many times do I have to tell you
that this is poison for your kidneys?
Swear to me that you didn't drink
a single drop of alcohol.
Did you drink?
It was just one tequila shot.
I'm done! I can't lift a finger without
your consent. I do everything wrong!
Sweetheart. you know
this is for your own good.
I'll never be normal again.
Don't say that.
One of us will be a match. I promise.
Mom promised too. and look at this.
I inherited this fucking syndrome
from you. This is all your fault.
I don't want to live like a prisoner.
following orders all the time.
I'm tired. I can't take it anymore!
Julieta…
Let her go.
She's right. though.
She inherited the worst of me.
Bernardo can't keep bringing
junk food into this house. Nana.
It's too tempting for Julieta.
There's not a single drop of alcohol
in this house. right?
No. ma'am.
I've even checked under the mattresses.
Like a prison!
Ma'am…
Finally. Julieta is out of the hospital.
I'm glad.
But Maca couldn't donate her kidney.
Her dad and brothers had to get tested.
but if they're not a match. we should go.
Listen. Victoria. I'm really sorry
about what's happening to Julieta.
but a kidney transplant
is a serious thing.
-And dangerous. too.
-And you get a huge scar. like this.
No way.
What about solidarity? Why are we friends
with the Sotomayors. then?
It's one thing to be friends.
but it's another thing to have one
of my daughters give up a kidney.
That's not happening!
You finally made it.
As usual. I was arguing with my mom.
How do you feel?
Like I need an urgent kidney transplant.
Other than that. I'm great.
Jerk.
I got FOMO from the after-party pics.
I can't believe I missed it.
I heard Camila left with two guys.
-No way! Two guys?
-Two guys.
I doubt I'm going to get anyone
to eat me before the worms do.
Speaking of guys. I made
some nice videos with you and your dad.
I can send them over so you can post them.
What for?
My last post only got seven likes.
We're not influencers. girl. Get over it.
Unless you post pics in your underwear
with your tits up here.
forget about the likes.
That doesn't sound so bad. you know?
But my mom would freak out.
She found my candy. I had to confess
I had one tequila shot at the party.
-You didn't tell her it was me?
-Of course not. She'd kill you.
She even told me
I can't drive the car they gave me.
With good reason. girl.
Imagine if you faint while driving.
That'd be an early grave for you.
Sorry. sorry. sorry.
It's not like I have
a long life ahead of me.
You're too much.
We have to do our best to stay calm.
Let's see what happens
with tomorrow's results.
If nobody's a match.
what are we going to do?
I checked the national donor center.
and there are 4.000 patients
ahead of Julieta.
So. that's not an option.
What about the hospital's private list?
We're doing better. but it'll take
at least six months to get anything.
Jiménez was very clear. Ricardo.
We're running out of time.
We have to be prepared
and raise as much money as possible.
Listen…
You sometimes operate on patients who are
seriously ill. even terminally ill. right?
And if one of those patients
had a kidney that was a match for Julieta.
maybe we could…
I don't know.
jump the hospital's waiting list and…
No…
-What?
-What are you talking about?
Do you understand what you're saying?
Then I won't tell you
what I was thinking about in the shower.
What were you thinking about
in the shower?
Organ trafficking.
How could you think of that?
Not only is it illegal. it's unethical.
We could go to jail.
If that's what I have to do
to save my daughter's life.
I don't care about jail.
Sure! You'll be able
to help her a lot more from jail.
Ricardo! Are you implying that
I don't care about my daughter's life?
I'm sorry. Forgive me. please. I'm upset.
I shouldn't have yelled. I'm sorry.
I just want to remind you…
that you taught me. and it's one
of the things I'm most grateful for.
that nothing is
more important than family.
This can't be right.
I'm not a match either?
Neither are the kids or Nana. Nobody.
We're not a match.
What about that syndrome?
Lorena called.
She said the DNA results will be ready
by the end of the day. at the latest.
Does Julieta know about this?
Gustavo and Bernardo
told me they wanted to tell her.
Good idea.
By the way. Emilio called me.
offering his help with anything we need.
Well. we need a kidney.
Yeah. I was thinking
about asking my parents.
They might still be donors. right?
If they're healthy. yeah.
The kids asked all their friends.
None of them volunteered. so…
This sucks. Ricardo.
They say you find out who your real
friends are when the going gets rough.
A donor has to show up
at some point. damn it.
Hello?
Hi. Maca. It's me.
I need to talk to you in private.
Come right away. please.
-Okay.
-And don't bring Ricardo.
Yes. got it.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Bye.
Jiménez. We have a surgery in two hours.
I need to get going now.
Okay.
Are you gonna tell me where we're going?
Time to try it out.
Go. Be careful.
The results are in.
Nobody is a match.
If I die. will you remember me forever?
You're not going to die.
Get that crap out of your head.
I heard my parents talking.
They're not gonna give up.
But you'll be left without an inheritance
if they keep spending on me.
As soon as you get better. open
an OnlyFans account to pay them off.
All right. let's toast.
To your health.
And as Dad says. two cheers.
because it's alcohol-free.
-Cheers. cheers.
-Cheers.
Thank you for being the best.
For the car surprise.
for lifting my spirits.
and for being such good brothers.
Now let's toast to something I don't have.
-To what?
-To my health.
Knock it off. Julieta.
Cheers.
Julieta is very depressed.
She could die. We have to help her.
What can we do for her. sweetie?
I already told her that giving up
her kidney is not a joke.
I'm of legal age. so I can do it.
And. as a matter of fact. I want to help--
At your age. you won't give away
your kidney to a high school classmate.
Besides. you don't know
if you'll still be friends in ten years.
Truth is. you don't even know
if you'll still be close to Julieta.
To give you some peace of mind.
I talked to Ricardo
and told him they can count on us.
That means getting tested
to see if we're a match.
Sweetie. this is the most important
project of my career!
It's a stadium
for 50.000 people in South Africa.
So a fucking stadium
is more important than Julieta's life?
-I didn't say that. I just--
-Thanks. Dad! That's great! Perfect.
Victoria. come here. Don't be rude.
-You two are impossible.
-It's fine. She'll get over it.
Young people think everything is forever.
Love. friendships. blood pacts…
The only cure for it is to grow up.
Victoria is light years away from that.
What is it?
-Hey.
-Why did you tell me not to bring Ricardo?
Your daughter has a new opportunity.
And my husband can't know about it?
The DNA results are in.
Neither your children
nor your husband have Alport syndrome.
That's good news!
Yes. but there's something else.
Something serious.
Even though we've known each other
for so long and we trust each other.
you still never told me.
Maca?
Maca. girl!
Maca. what's wrong?
I just found out…
that Julieta is not my husband's daughter.
We're in the house of the mom with
the record for the world's biggest bump!
It was huge!
And the most beautiful bump!
-How big is your bump?
-That's you!
-Don't measure it!
-What do you think?
Three meters!
Bernardo! He's so cute!
-Pee.
-No!
I love it.
Now? Boys. let's go.
-Calm down. Let's breathe.
-I'll get the bag. Where is it?
-Where's the bag? The bag!
-Boys?
Don't forget the bag.
-Don't leave my side.
-The keys?
This video made my day. Dad.
And I have a private collection
you've never seen before.
I want to see them all.
Sure.
That way I forget that I'm sick.
and I'm reminded I have
the best parents in the world.
And we have the bravest
and most badass daughter in the world.
Hey. love.
-Hi. sweetie.
-Hi.
The surgery is already finished?
It got canceled.
That's great.
How are you feeling. sweetie?
Well. I found out neither my dad.
nor my nanny. nor my siblings are a match.
But the DNA results came in.
Nobody has the syndrome.
Just you and me.
I'm your clone. They say the last child
always gets the leftovers.
Julieta…
-Victoria's here. See you tonight.
-Take care. sweetheart.
Hey. stop.
Don't make that face. love.
Look at me.
I'm her dad.
and I can't give her my kidney either.
I have to tell you something.
Yeah. sure. What is it?
What is it. Maca?
It's just that…
It's nothing. That video got to me.
Sometimes the past comes back
and hits you really hard.
Julieta is our miracle child.
She saved our marriage. honey.
No. Bernardo! Stop!
-Don't do that. Give me the spoon.
-Mom. I want milk.
No. sweetie. Do you want milk?
Yes. I'll give you some milk. Wait.
Hey. guys! Dad's here!
What's up. Maca?
I made a thousand pesos.
and I brought the diapers you…
Shit. I left them on the bus. sorry.
Don't swear in front of the children!
We need to talk.
My mom died six months ago.
She was the only one
who helped me with the kids.
I take two-minute showers. Ricardo.
with the kids in the bathroom. of course.
I couldn't enroll this semester
because we can't even afford daycare.
We had to move back
to the place my mom used to live in.
My career went down the drain!
My life went down the drain
because my husband lives from bar to bar.
from serenade to serenade.
and from drink to drink!
-You're drunk!
-Maca. wait. I promise you I--
No! I've fucking had it
with your promises!
I've fucking had it!
You're not the man I married.
the one I made a thousand plans with.
If I have to feel alone.
I'd rather be alone.
What do you mean?
I want a divorce.
I won't drink ever again. Maca. okay?
I promise you. please.
but let me show you I can change.
Weren't you going
to a high school reunion?
No. I told Lorena I couldn't go.
No! You need to clear your head. please.
Go. I'll stay with the kids.
What?
The kids don't take care of themselves!
Maca. please!
If you don't trust me one last time.
how can I show you
what I'm capable of doing for all of you?
Maca. everything will be different
when you come back.
Come on. girl. Relax.
Five calls in three hours. really?
Ricardo put you on the phone with
your in-laws. and they're with the kids.
Yeah. that was reassuring.
Look. you have two options.
You either relax and we have fun.
or you go back to Mexico City.
but not like this. Macaroni.
Right? Yeah. you're right. Okay.
I'll relax. I even feel like dancing.
That's more like it!
Let's go somewhere else.
It was him! Of course it was him!
Maca?
Sorry. we weren't told that…
Are you okay?
We need to talk about Julieta now.
-Emilio…
-Okay. about what?
I'd ask how you're doing.
but your face says it all.
Come in. please.
I'm so sorry
you can't give your daughter your kidney.
-Like I told Ricardo--
-Yes. I know. but that's not all of it.
Something came up that…
I mean. I didn't see it coming.
I didn't know. I…
Maca. you're scaring us.
Please. you know you can tell us anything.
What happened?
Neither Ricardo nor the kids were a match.
That's why we need a private donor.
because if this takes too long.
my daughter could die.
-No.
-No…
-Don't say that.
-That won't happen.
It won't happen.
Please. excuse me. I need to go.
but I'm sure someone will come along.
You know what?
I came here to find that someone.
We've asked…
all our friends for help.
Emilio. could you please
take the test to see if you're a match?
It's important.
Of course. you too. Please.
Listen. Maca. I understand
what you're going through. but…
I'll be completely honest with you.
I'm about to deliver the most important
project of my life. I don't have time--
It takes less than an hour. Emilio.
Look. Maca. unfortunately. we can't
guarantee that we'll take the test.
But why don't you give us
some time to discuss it?
Right…
Sure. I understand.
I trust in our friendship.
Above all. I trust in
our daughters' friendship.
I'll be waiting for you
at the hospital tomorrow. Thank you.
I'll walk you out.
I feel for them.
This can't be easy for Maca and Ricardo.
What's with that look?
Emilio. please. Don't try to fool me.
That woman came to talk to you.
No. That woman
came to ask us to get tested.
No. she came to ask you to get tested.
She was looking at you and talking to you.
I hate it when
you blow things out of proportion.
Maca is still in love with you.
It's obvious.
Please. What are you talking about?
I'm not stupid!
I might look and act stupid. but I'm not!
How can you say she's in love with me
when she ended the relationship?
She dumped me
and didn't want to hear from me again.
and that happened ages ago!
And we didn't see each other again
until our daughters met in school.
Do I need to spell it out for you?
-I've got a good nose for these things.
-Maybe COVID fucked it up.
I can't deal with the jealousy.
and your dad is waiting for me.
If we get tested
and one of us happens to be a match.
Ricardo and Maca
will pressure us to be donors.
and to protect my daughters.
I won't allow--
That's enough! Enough!
That's a ten!
Yeah? Is it cool?
You just need an accessory
to cover the patch but…
How does it look from above?
You want me to take pictures of you
lying down? Let's see…
Just tell me how it looks.
Weird. but creative.
Hold this for me for a sec. please.
Sorry. Grandma. we've been neglecting you.
Mom's been very busy with me.
Grandma Lucía died before I was born.
She had a heart attack.
Mom says she missed her a lot back then.
but she doesn't remember much anymore.
The longer you've been dead.
the less your loved ones miss you.
When I get a place here. will you visit?
At least for my birthday.
Come on. Give me a break.
You're not going to die. Julieta!
You have one job.
I want to be buried in this dress.
Did you make me come with you
to buy your funeral dress?
If I'd told you. you wouldn't have come.
It'd be embarrassing if everyone saw me
in white and found out I died a virgin.
I'm out. You're crazy! Crazy!
What if I'm cremated instead
to save money?
ESTUDIO DÍAZ
ARCHITECTS
Thank you.
Your brother-in-law is running his mouth.
saying Mr. Díaz will give him the stadium.
Once my father-in-law sees this.
he'll be floored.
I'm the best architect in this firm.
and he knows it.
-Help me cover it.
-This model of yours looks amazing.
But don't get too cocky.
-Okay.
-Family is family.
Good morning. Sergio.
My dad wants to see us both. brother.
Are you his messenger now or what?
The South Africans think
we need their stadium project.
but we have to make them think
that they need us.
You both have to be
at the top of your game.
Don't worry. Dad.
I'm proposing a design
that's very innovative. efficient--
Save the details for the presentation.
If they choose us. one of you is getting
1% of the total construction costs.
That means millions.
May the best man win.
My friend Victoria says that…
I'm not an influencer because I don't post
pictures or videos in my underwear.
Well. today I'm going to show you
my underwear
and something better.
I'm going to make a fool of myself!
But. honestly. I don't care.
because it's just…
It's just the five of you.
Okay. These two tubes right here…
Let me get them out.
Here they are. These tubes you see here…
Can you see them? Okay.
These two tubes right here
are keeping me alive.
And I connect them to this machine.
which filters my blood…
three times a week.
I sit here and wait until it's done.
Well. I've had kidney problems
since I was 15.
and if I don't find a donor soon. well…
I'm royally screwed.
In this case. I'd be renally screwed.
One second. give me a second.
I want to show you what I bought today…
This! Isn't it beautiful?
Wait a second. Let me put it on.
How does it look?
Doesn't it look great?
I love it! I love it! I love it!
Let's see…
I've never had so many people online.
Well…
Thank you. everyone. for saying
positive things. and fuck the haters!
Did you know there are millions of people
with the same problem I have.
so there aren't enough donors?
So it wouldn't hurt if some of you
decided to sign up as donors.
That way. when you kick the bucket.
you could help sick people like me.
Am I going to do another LIVE like this?
Well. I don't know.
Maybe you'll be the last ones
to see me live
because tomorrow I could wake up dead.
Yeah. my kidneys are so messed up
they could take me out at any moment.
Well. I won't say anything else
because TikTok might ban me and…
I'm starting to feel a bit anxious.
so I'm wrapping up the LIVE.
Thanks so much. friends.
and see you next time.
if there is one.
All right. bye.
Maca! I've been looking for you
since I got here!
-Did you see your daughter's LIVE?
-No.
Brace yourself.
…I've had kidney problems since I was 15.
and if I don't find a donor soon.
I'm royally screwed.
They'll be online any minute.
According to the schedule.
you start. Emilio.
-Yes. sir.
-It's night over there.
I need everyone
to be full of energy. okay?
I'm ready. Carlos.
-I'm ready too. Dad--
-Yeah. yeah.
What is it. Pedro?
Sorry. Carlos. I need to make
some adjustments to the presentation.
-I won't be long. One minute. please.
-Seriously. man?
You can't just show up like this!
What makes you think you can
threaten Pedro so I come talk to you?
I'm in the most important meeting
of my life--
Julieta is your daughter.
and she needs you to donate your kidney!
1 IN EVERY 25 FATHERS
IS RAISING ANOTHER'S MAN CHILD.
AND IN MOST CASES.
THEY NEVER FIND OUT.
Subtitle translation by: Alicia Núñez